The animated House Musical.
Interstella 5555: The 5tory of the 5ecret 5tar 5ystem is a animation,
science fiction, music film directed by Kazuhisa Takenouchi.
Four talented alien musicians are kidnapped by a record
producer who disguises them as humans.
Shep, a space pilot in love with bass player Stella, follows them to Earth.
Reprogrammed to forget their real identities and renamed The Crescendolls, the
group quickly becomes a huge success playing soulless corporate pop.
At a concert, Shep manages to free all the musicians except Stella, and the band
sets out to rediscover who they really are — and to rescue Stella.
Octave (singing voice), played by Romanthony.
Shep (singing voice), played by Thomas Bangalter.
Interstella 5555: The 5tory of the 5ecret 5tar 5ystem (インターステラ5555, Intāsutera Fō
Faibu; "Four Five") is a 2003 anime musical science fiction film.
The film tells the story of the abduction and rescue of an extraterrestrial pop band and
serves as a visual companion to Discovery, Daft Punk's second studio album.
The film was produced by Toei Animation, directed by Kazuhisa
Takenouchi and supervised by Leiji Matsumoto.
The film has no dialogue, but instead consists of the
entirety of Discovery with minimal sound effects.
The film explores themes of rescue, spaceman,
musical, record producer, music video.
The tone is thought_provoking.